export const countryCapitalQuiz = {
    heading: 'Asian Country Capital Quiz',
    quiz: [
        {
            question: 'Which is the capital of India?',
            options: ['New Delhi', 'Mumbai', 'Punjab', 'Benguluru'],
            correctAnswer: 'New Delhi'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which is the capital of Bhutan?',
            options: ['Tawang', 'Thimpu', 'Tripura', 'Nepal'],
            correctAnswer: 'Thimpu'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which is the capital of China?',
            options: ['Chengdu', 'Shanghai', 'Shenzhen', 'Bejing'],
            correctAnswer: 'Bejing'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which is the capital of Pakistan?',
            options: ['Islamabad', 'Karachi', 'Lahore', 'Sindh'],
            correctAnswer: 'Islamabad'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which is the capital of Nepal?',
            options: ['Bhutan', 'Kathmandu', 'Thimpu', 'Shimla'],
            correctAnswer: 'Kathmandu'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which is the capital of Israel?',
            options: ['Jerusalem', 'Tel-Aviv', 'Lod', 'Acre'],
            correctAnswer: 'Jerusalem'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which is the capital of Iran?',
            options: ['Shiraz', 'Manchester', 'Urmia', 'Tehran'],
            correctAnswer: 'Tehran'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which is the capital of Bangladesh?',
            options: ['Sunderban', 'Dhaka', 'Chittagaon', 'Barishal'],
            correctAnswer: 'Dhaka'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which is the capital of Azerbaijan?',
            options: ['Baku', 'Manama', 'Muscat', 'Moscow'],
            correctAnswer: 'Baku'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which is the capital of Philippines?',
            options: ['Sydeny', 'Manila', 'Melbourne', 'Perth'],
            correctAnswer: 'Manila'
        }
    ]
} 